好  不要妨碍他们做事
Okay, stay out of their way
也别再回答任何问题
and don't answer any more questions.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
去撤销搜查令
To quash the warrant.
法官阁下
Your Honor!
-为什么你要大喊大叫  -我没有
- Why are you yelling? - I'm not yelling.
我动了真感情  法官阁下
I'm passionate, Your Honor.
这起案件是感情引导的
The abuse here is passion-inducing.
感情引导
Passion-inducing?
我的天  我们不要被感情所引导
Well, goodness, let's not have our passion induced.
让我把话说明白
So let me get this straight...
你要我不让他代表他
you want me to bar him from representing him.
这就是你要求的补偿吗
That's your requested remedy?
是的  法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
达米安·博伊不仅仅代表
Damian Boyle is not just representing
杰拉蒂犯罪家族
the Gerraghty crime family.
-他就是其中的一员  -怎么说
- He's a member of the Gerraghty crime family. - Why,